http://www.btsb.com/privacy-statement

Privacy Policy
Personally Identifiable InformationSimply visiting the Bound to Stay Bound Books website does not require you to disclose any information about yourself. However, on occasion Bound to Stay Bound Books may require additional details about you, such as your name, address, and email address. Please be advised that we can only collect this information when you voluntarily submit it to us as part of a contact us communication or order submission. We will use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to fulfill your communications request. It is Bound to Stay Bound Books policy not to sell, rent or lease any personally identifiable information.External LinksLinks to third-party websites may be available from the Bound to Stay Bound Books website. If you decide to use these links, you will leave the Bound to Stay Bound Books website. Please be aware that Bound to Stay Bound Books does not control these websites. Thus, Bound to Stay Bound Books is not responsible for the content of these sites or their privacy policies. Acceptance of the Privacy Policy by utilizing the Bound to Stay Bound Books website, you consent to the terms contained in this Privacy Policy and to any subsequently posted changes to the Privacy Policy. Bound to Stay Bound Books may update or change this Privacy Policy at any time. In doing so, any and all changes will be posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at btsb@btsb.com.
